const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'What type of car do Harry and Ron fly to Hogwarts in their 2nd year?',
        answers: [
            'Ford Zephyr',
            'Cadillac Deville',
            'Ford Anglia',
            'Ford Zodiac'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Ford Anglia',
        image: 'https://pa1.narvii.com/6479/1816e689d4b1c51c0e5fb93ac35b92e9120a7f01_hq.gif',
        alt: 'Ford Anglia car flying through the air with mountain and clouds in the background'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of Filch\'s cat?',
        answers: [
            'Kitten',
            'Miss Squibbles',
            'Mr. Nick',
            'Mrs. Norris'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Mrs. Norris',
        image: 'http://s3.crackedcdn.com/phpimages/article/0/4/3/602043_v2.gif',
        alt: 'Filch dancing with Mrs. Norris the cat'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the oldest Weasley son?',
        answers: [
            'Bill',
            'Charlie',
            'Percy',
            'Ron'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Bill',
        image: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/b3c5464921cd81654ce9583b8ddef570/tumblr_pa90yfZCTF1ulbitho1_250.gif',
        alt: 'Bill Weasley setting down a cup'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who teaches Divination classes at Hogwarts?',
        answers: [
            'Sybill Trelawney',
            'Horace Slughorn',
            'Pomona Sprout',
            'Filius Flitwick'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Sybill Trelawney',
        image: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/669daba5a0f80f188492d31ebb227b13/tumblr_o1wgzaqiXe1sfmnojo1_500.gif',
        alt: 'Professor Trelawney with her arms in the air'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the model of Harry\'s first broom?',
        answers: [
            'Firebolt',
            'Nimbus 2000',
            'Cleansweep 11',
            'Comet Two Sixty'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Nimbus 2000',
        image: 'https://thumbs.gfycat.com/InstructiveFragrantArmedcrab-size_restricted.gif',
        alt: 'Harry Potter flying a Nimbus 2000 in a Quidditch match'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of Hermione\'s cat?',
        answers: [
            'Scabbers',
            'Hedwig',
            'Crookshanks',
            'Sirius'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Crookshanks',
        image: 'https://media1.tenor.com/images/f635dcd5b41d91abe3f5815cf616fa56/tenor.gif',
        alt: 'Crookshanks the cat sitting on a pile of books'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the form of Harry\'s patronus?',
        answers: [
            'Stag',
            'Doe',
            'Otter',
            'Phoenix'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Stag',
        image: 'https://68.media.tumblr.com/246f2d4e802dc53cb978d11ff7a9c1b4/tumblr_oepe870vPj1v7vro0o1_500.gif',
        alt: 'The white glowing form of a stag'
    },
    {
        question: 'What type of monster is hidden in the Chamber of Secrets?',
        answers: [
            'Giant Spider',
            'Basilisk',
            'Dragon',
            'Dementor'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Basilisk',
        image: 'https://img.buzzfeed.com/buzzfeed-static/static/2015-09/14/19/enhanced/webdr09/anigif_enhanced-29192-1442274062-2.gif?crop=245:162;0,28}',
        alt: 'A giant Basilisk snake from Harry Potter'
    },
    {
        question: 'What position does Harry play on the Gryffindor Quidditch team?',
        answers: [
            'Beater',
            'Chaser',
            'Keeper',
            'Seeker'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Seeker',
        image: 'https://tuesdayswithhorry.files.wordpress.com/2014/07/snitch-gif.gif',
        alt: 'Harry Potter reaching for the golden snitch'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the \'Half-blood Prince\' ?',
        answers: [
            'Severus Snape',
            'Draco Malfoy',
            'Lucious Malfoy',
            'Tom Riddle'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Severus Snape',
        image: 'http://66.media.tumblr.com/082265ba82eb5887ad348fcedd6575b0/tumblr_nmjjijhnH91qec7ceo1_500.gif',
        alt: 'Snape deflecting a spell with his wand'
    },
];